

Javier Alejandro Cuesta Narvaez Computer technician



A Coruña, Galicia-España. CP 15141. 684657561

javicn14@gmail.com

14/04/1988

https://www.linkedin.com/in/javicn14

Professional objective

I am a computer professional with knowledge and experience in maintenance of computer equipment, software and hardware and management of Windows and Linux operating systems with knowledge of PowerShell, Microsoft Azure Intune, Airwhatch, SCCM, Routing and. My professional goals in the long term are focused on consolidating a professional profile as a Software Architect. I am interested in developing my skills in a work environment that demands teamwork, initiative, and organizational and research skills.

Professional experience

2019 – ACT Technical Support of Computer Systems N2 for CAU-

INDITEX - Oesia

2018 -2019. Operations Help Desk. Teleperformance

2017-Act. Web Developer and Systems Technician as FreeLancer

2014-2016 Systems Technician at Hardware and Software level in

Inversiones Reycus 1083, C.A.

Academic training

2010-2016 **Systems Engineer.** Universidad Santa María . Caracas-Venezuela.

2002-2007 High School U. E. P. BELAGUA. Venezuela

Complementary training

2018 Assembly operations and maintenance of microcomputer systems. Classroom Nosa (300 hrs)

2017 Mobile APP development. Universidad Complutense de Madrid. (40 horas)

2017 Course Java. Bellinsoft (40 horas)

2017 Course Javascript. Sololearn (40 horas)

2017 Bitcoin: concepts, technology and uses. UNIMOOC (40 horas)

Digital skills

MS Office	
Google	
Windows	
MS Intune	00000
Cmd / Bash	
HTML5	••••
CCS3	
Javascript	
Wordpress	
Powershell	
C++	
MySQL	
SQLServer	
Putty	
Citrix	••••
Networking	••••

Languages



Nivel B1

Labor Competencies

Continuous learning
Communication skills
Assumption responsibilities
Teamwork
Organization and planning
elaboration of technical
documentation and analysis
of work methodologies